# Ciaran Kearney - Software Engineer

Based: Maastricht, Netherlands. Email: <u>ckearney1992@gmail.com</u>

Phone Number: +31655913767

Portfolio: <u>www.kearmododragon.com</u>

Github Repo: <a href="https://github.com/kearmododragon">https://github.com/kearmododragon</a>
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/ciarankearney92/

I am a Software Engineer who enjoys problem solving and being customer focused. I have over 10 years of experience in customer service at multiple brands which has helped develop my adaptability, critical thinking and problem solving no matter the challenge. I hope to continue leaving a positive impact everywhere I go and look forward to bringing my up-beat personality into my next team.

I am a confident, outgoing individual who is capable of taking on new challenges. This can be seen in me leaving my school to take A levels at an independent sixth form and taking the final year of my degree in Barcelona. I am self-motivated and driven to succeed with an impeccable attendance at work, with my only time off over my working life being due to a severe knee injury. One of the things I am truly passionate about is embracing situations that are outside of my comfort zone and testing myself. Travelling and immersing myself in different cultures, such as working abroad, allows me to achieve this.

## Work experience:

Mercedes-Benz CAC, Maastricht.

Dealer Parts Support Logistic Specialist

May, 2021 - Present

May, 2021 - Present

- Promoted to a new department during covid lockdowns.
- involved in multiple projects, including improving the work atmosphere based on an annual questionnaire.
- Quickly established myself as a valuable team member both as a knowledge base and socially.
- Handling high priority cases from the UK and Ireland but assisting the European market.

Senior Customer Service Representative

September, 2018 - April, 2021

- Promoted to a senior role after 16 months.
- handling high profile cases such as complaints to the Board of Management, international cases, manager escalations of cases and long term breakdowns.
- Training new starters on the market.

Customer Service Representative

May, 2017 - August, 2017

- Moved from the UK to the Netherlands to take the role.
- Direct customer contact including written and verbal.
- Further developed the ability to think on my feet in order to problem solve.
- Entrusted with assisting the training of new starters.

Books Hostel, Rio de Janeiro

November, 2016-December, 2016

. General Assistant

- I travelled to Brazil in 2016.
- Worked in a hostel in order to prolong my stay.
- In charge of booking in/out customers, complaint handling and activities outside of the hostel.

## The Navigation, Newark

May, 2015 - September, 2016

Assistant Bar Manager

- Built up my position within the bar to become an Assistant Bar Manager within the first year of working.
- Entrusted with opening/closing the bar, ensuring the bar was staffed and cashed up.
- Created a stock-take system.
- Lead the interview process and onboarding for new members of staff.
- Developed my communication, problem solving and management skills.

#### Previous experience:

Carlson Wagonlit Business Tourism Company, Staffordshire University Student Union Shop, Burghley Horse Trials, Wilkinson, Volunteer at Newark Town Football Club.

#### **Education**

# **General Assembly**

Software Engineering Immersive

February, 2023 - May, 2023

- 420 hour fully immersive course
- Developed knowledge and use of Javascript, Full Stack Development, Python,
- Course taken remotely and completed alongside my full time job

#### Staffordshire University

Tourism Management

- 4 year Tourism Management course
- Final year taken in Barcelona with ESERP Business School
- Third year taken as a placement with Carlson Wagonlit to ensure that I had the real world experience in the sector

Prior education taken at NCN High Pavement Sixth Form College, Nottingham and All Saints Catholic School, Mansfield.

## **Key Skills:**

- Football coaching and Referee.

I have coached in the UK and in the Netherlands, taking on a girls team most recently. Helping me judge character and ability, tailor how I handle people in situations and work on motivational skills on an individual level.

- Self Confidence and Leadership.

Through my years I've had various hurdles in my personal life, however I've been able to maintain a level of self confidence. I'll always be looking for negative feedback so that I'm able to improve regardless of what it's regarding without taking it personally.